Contact

dswilkins@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/daniellewilkins-bsn-rn-145a39133 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Healthcare Patient Safety

Danielle Wilkins, BSN, RN

Pediatric Travel RN || Epic Go Live Support || Travel Nurse Mentor Greater Denver Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the staffing and recruiting industry. Skilled in Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Healthcare, Patient Safety, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Customer Service. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science.

Experience

Children's Hospital Colorado Registered Nurse August 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Aya Healthcare Registered Nurse December 2013 - Present (6 years 7 months)

St. Louis Children's Hospital Epic Go Live Consulant May 2018 - June 2018 (2 months) Greater St. Louis Area

The HCI Group Epic support April 2018 - June 2018 (3 months) Rochester, Minnesota Area

Mayo Clinic Rochester Epic Go Live Consultant May 2018 - May 2018 (1 month)

Rochester, Minnesota

Intermountain Healthcare Registered Nurse May 2017 - August 2017 (4 months) Salt Lake City, Utah

Rady Children's Hospital-San Diego Registered Nurse January 2017 - April 2017 (4 months) San Diego, California

PROVIDENCE SACRED HEART MEDICAL CNTR AND CHILDRENS

Registered Nurse September 2016 - December 2016 (4 months) Spokane, Washington

Children's Mercy Kansas City Registered Nurse December 2014 - April 2015 (5 months) Kansas City, Missouri

Texas Children's Hospital Registered Nurse March 2014 - December 2014 (10 months) Katy, Texas

Riley Hospital for Children
Registered Nurse
May 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 8 months)
Indianapolis, Indiana

Education

Ball State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011)

North Park University
Associate of Science - AS, Psychology · (2007)